<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on Notes for self made anime</title><link>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on Notes for self made anime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 13:08:16 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blender</title><link>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/blender/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 13:08:16 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/blender/</guid><description>Written in December 2021, with Blender 2.93 or 3.0.
Modeling Basics In order to set real-world size, enable Viewport Overlays &amp;gt; Measurement &amp;gt; Edge length during &amp;quot;Edit mode&amp;quot; and show the size of meshes. See this StackExchange answer for more details. To hide a mesh in an edit mode, H: To hide the selected mesh Shift H: To hide everything but the selected mesh Alt H: To unhide everything This information is from this article.</description></item><item><title>VRoid Studio</title><link>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/vroid_studio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 13:08:16 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/vroid_studio/</guid><description>Export There are multiple options for License. In order to understand each license option, the wikipedia is most useful to understand.</description></item><item><title>Animation</title><link>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/animation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 13:38:20 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/animation/</guid><description>General Color Skin color pallete
Anime CGing Tutorial: Color Choice Skin color palette Color palette for skin, hair, and eyes Real Skin Tones Color Scheme Skin colors European Example 1 from Anime CGing Tutorial.
base: #ecc4b8 shadow: #c78d7d highlight: #f8e9e6 2D animation Adobe After Effects is mainly described in this page.
How to show that a camera moves on one image Scale in/out the image Change the position of the image How to organize assets Use pre-compose.</description></item><item><title>Basics</title><link>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/basics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 01:51:07 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/basics/</guid><description>Fonts How to choose fonts See this video for details Best 10 fonts for editings See this video for details Web service to browse a lot of fonts at the same time wordmark.it Image There is a tool to remove a background from an image, https://www.remove.bg/, if you want to clip images and use them somewhere. It's better to color edges of the clipped image like by a white color to use it</description></item><item><title>Video Editing</title><link>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/video-editing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 14:57:41 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/video-editing/</guid><description>This is written in March 2021.
In this page, Adobe Premiere Pro is mostly described.
Workflow If you make a video from multiple other videos, then
Prepare source videos Clip some videos to make import time shorter and easy to edit ffmpeg might be helpful to do this Import them into Premiere Pro Ingest settings: Use Proxy Codec: Apple ProRes or DNxHR Edit a video Codec Format H.</description></item><item><title>Digital paintings</title><link>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/digital-painting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 14:12:20 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://michael-freling.github.io/docs/digital-painting/</guid><description>This page is written on July 2020.
For anime-style digital painting, these 2 channels are really helpful for wide topics, especially if you understand Japanese.
YouTube: さいとうなおきチャンネル YouTube: Deep Blizzard's Art School In this page, you can see some links to videos on the above 2 channels, but in their videos, Japanese is mainly spoken and no English translations is added.
Styles There are some styles to paint colors.</description></item></channel></rss>